<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on Matthew Peyton</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on Matthew Peyton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <managingEditor>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2017-2024 Matthew Peyton</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:29:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Legume Free Butter Chicken</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/legume_free_butter_chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:29:50 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/legume_free_butter_chicken/</guid>
      <description>Legume Free Butter Chicken Adapted from this recipe.&#xA;This is legume free in the sense that it does not have any Fenugreek.&#xA;Ingredients For the chicken marinade:&#xA;28 oz (800g) boneless and skinless chicken thighs or breasts cut into bite-sized pieces 1/2 cup plain yogurt 1 1/2 tablespoons minced garlic 1 tablespoon minced ginger (or finely grated) 2 teaspoons garam masala 1 teaspoon turmeric 1 teaspoon ground cumin 1 teaspoon red chili powder 1 teaspoon of salt For the sauce:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baked Honey Salmon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/baked_honey_salmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:39:06 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/baked_honey_salmon/</guid>
      <description>Baked Honey Salmon Ingredients 1 pound Salmon Filet 1 Tablespoon Honey Salt and Pepper Basmati Rice Broccoli Instructions Heat oven to 400F Cook rice and steam broccoli in rice cooker Place salmon (skin side down) on baking pan Place directly on pan. NO parchment or tinfoil. Spread honey on salmon Season salmon with salt and pepper Bake salmon 7-10 minutes Turn on broiler, run for 5-7 minutes IMPORTANT: Constantly monitor while broiling to prevent burning....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Crunchwrap Supreme</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/homemade_crunchwrap_supreme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:19:03 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/homemade_crunchwrap_supreme/</guid>
      <description>Homemade Crunchwrap Supreme Inspired by this Reddit post.&#xA;Ingredients 1 Burrito-sized flour tortilla 1 Taco-sized flour tortilla 1 Taco-sized corn tortilla Ground beef Taco seasoning Pepper jack nacho cheese Greek yogurt OR sour cream OR guacamole Shredded lettuce Diced tomato Instructions Shred the lettuce and dice the tomatoes. Season the ground beef and cook it. Construct the layers: First layer: Burrito sized tortilla. Second layer: Seasoned ground beef spread out from center....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Chicken Parm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/slow_cooker_chicken_parm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 23:41:34 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/slow_cooker_chicken_parm/</guid>
      <description>Slow Cooker Chicken Parm Ingredients 2x Chicken Breast Packs (4 breasts) 1 Cans Trader Joes Marinara Sauce 1 Can Trader Joe&amp;rsquo;s Vodka Sauce Pasta (Spaghetti) Salt and Pepper Instructions Mix both sauces into slow cooker Season chicken breasts with salt and pepper Place chicken breasts in slow cooker, submerging underneath sauce Cover and set to LOW for 4 hours Do NOT lock the lid in place with the clasps After 3....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Tortilla Soup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/chicken_tortilla_soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:28:25 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/chicken_tortilla_soup/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Tortilla Soup Ingredients Tortilla chips / strips 1 Tbsp olive oil 1 medium onion, chopped 3 garlic cloves, minced 1 jalapeno pepper , seeded and diced 1 tsp ground cumin 1 tsp chilli powder 1 lb chicken breasts, (2 medium) 20 oz can crushed tomatoes 32 oz chicken broth 14 oz can black beans, drained and rinsed 1/2 cup cilantro, chopped, divided (reserve 1/4 of it for garnish) 1 lime, juiced 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 large avocado, diced 1 lime, cut into wedges, to serve Instructions Finely chop onion, garlic, jalapeño....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baked Honey Granola</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/baked_honey_granola/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:22:28 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/baked_honey_granola/</guid>
      <description>Baked Honey Granola Ingredients 2 Cups uncooked rolled oats Quarter cup brown sugar (or regular sugar) Do an eigth of a cup for less sweet granola Quarter teaspoon cinnamon Quarter cup of honey Quarter cup of olive oil Pinch of salt (Optional) Any dried mixins (e.g. dried fruit) Instructions Preheat oven to 325 degrees In large bowl, combine oats, brown sugar, cinnamon, salt In a glass measuring cup, add honey, and warm in microwave for 30 seconds Add the olive oil to the honey and stir to mix Drizzle the honey+olive oil over the ingredients....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>