<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Matthew Peyton</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Matthew Peyton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <managingEditor>inquiries@mpeyton.com (Matthew Peyton)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>inquiries@mpeyton.com (Matthew Peyton)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2017-2024 Matthew Peyton</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 22:41:01 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Computer I Want</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the_computer_i_want/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 22:41:01 -0800</pubDate><author>inquiries@mpeyton.com (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the_computer_i_want/</guid>
      <description>I have a very clear idea of what my &amp;ldquo;ideal&amp;rdquo; computer would be. It would incorporate all of the best aspects of the different computers I already use today, into a single machine.&#xA;The What First, it would have the form factor of a typical smartphone. This would allow me to carry it everywhere, and use it both one-handed and two-handed. I might even have it be a “hotdog-style foldable” to allow for comfier reading....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Switched From Local Plaintext Accounting to SaaS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/plaintext_accounting_to_saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 23:08:10 -0800</pubDate><author>inquiries@mpeyton.com (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/plaintext_accounting_to_saas/</guid>
      <description>Before 2017, I was a user of Mint for tracking my personal finances. However, around that time, I realized that it didn&amp;rsquo;t offer me much functionality. Worse, it was storing my banking and investment account credentials in a way that allowed server-side decryption. (In order to do browser automation and screen scraping of financial websites) So I decided to switch to something else.&#xA;2017 was also the year when I decided to start using more Free and Open Source Software in my life....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Programmatically Bookmark, Archive and Share Websites</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/programmatic_bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 22:31:19 -0800</pubDate><author>inquiries@mpeyton.com (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/programmatic_bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>For the last decade plus, I’ve been tossing links to interesting pages in all sorts of random places. Firefox bookmarks, Apple Notes, Apple Reminders, Markdown files, emails to myself…&#xA;I figured it was finally time to organize all of that. Plus I’ve also wanted to add more content to my personal website for awhile. With my bookmarked links now organized in a single place, it was easy to auto-generate my bookmarks page....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>