<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Matthew Peyton</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Matthew Peyton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <managingEditor>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2017-2024 Matthew Peyton</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:45:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Things Already Done Are Still Worth Doing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things_already_done_are_still_worth_doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:45:51 -0700</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things_already_done_are_still_worth_doing/</guid>
      <description>Things Already Done Are Still Worth Doing&#xA;It seems like everything has already been done. Just about every storyline, business idea, photograph, English sentence and more have already been done. It’s estimated that there are about 100 billion unique humans that have ever lived. About 8 billion of them are alive right now. That’s a lot of people doing a lot of things. It’s likely, almost guaranteed, that at least one of them has already done the thing you want to do....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My 35 Database Opinions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my_35_database_opinions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:11:22 -0700</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my_35_database_opinions/</guid>
      <description>“That’s just, like, your opinion, man.” - The Dude&#xA;Like all opinions, some of these might be wrong, and some might be right. Some might only apply in certain circumstances. But these are the opinions I’ve formed over the last 5+ years on what databases to use, and how to use them.&#xA;Pick relational databases by default. “NoSQL” means “another one-off query language to learn”. Only use alternative databases (MongoDB, Redis, Cassandra, etc....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legume Free Butter Chicken</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/legume_free_butter_chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:29:50 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/legume_free_butter_chicken/</guid>
      <description>Legume Free Butter Chicken Adapted from this recipe.&#xA;This is legume free in the sense that it does not have any Fenugreek.&#xA;Ingredients For the chicken marinade:&#xA;28 oz (800g) boneless and skinless chicken thighs or breasts cut into bite-sized pieces 1/2 cup plain yogurt 1 1/2 tablespoons minced garlic 1 tablespoon minced ginger (or finely grated) 2 teaspoons garam masala 1 teaspoon turmeric 1 teaspoon ground cumin 1 teaspoon red chili powder 1 teaspoon of salt For the sauce:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Ideal Libre Computer&#43;Phone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my_ideal_libre_computer_phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 22:41:01 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my_ideal_libre_computer_phone/</guid>
      <description>I have a very clear idea of what my &amp;ldquo;ideal&amp;rdquo; computer would be. It would incorporate all of the best aspects of the different computers (including smartphones!) I already use today, into a single machine.&#xA;The What First, it would have the form factor of a typical smartphone. This would allow me to carry it everywhere, and use it both one-handed and two-handed. I might even have it be a “hotdog-style foldable” to allow for comfier reading....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Switched From Local Plaintext Accounting to a SaaS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/plaintext_accounting_to_saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 23:08:10 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/plaintext_accounting_to_saas/</guid>
      <description>Before 2017, I was a user of Mint for tracking my personal finances. However, around that time, I realized that it didn&amp;rsquo;t offer me much functionality. Worse, it was storing my banking and investment account credentials in a way that allowed server-side decryption. (In order to do browser automation and screen scraping of financial websites) So I decided to switch to something else.&#xA;2017 was also the year when I decided to start using more Free and Open Source Software in my life....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baked Honey Salmon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/baked_honey_salmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:39:06 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/baked_honey_salmon/</guid>
      <description>Baked Honey Salmon Ingredients 1 pound Salmon Filet 1 Tablespoon Honey Salt and Pepper Basmati Rice Broccoli Instructions Heat oven to 400F Cook rice and steam broccoli in rice cooker Place salmon (skin side down) on baking pan Place directly on pan. NO parchment or tinfoil. Spread honey on salmon Season salmon with salt and pepper Bake salmon 7-10 minutes Turn on broiler, run for 5-7 minutes IMPORTANT: Constantly monitor while broiling to prevent burning....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Crunchwrap Supreme</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/homemade_crunchwrap_supreme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:19:03 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/homemade_crunchwrap_supreme/</guid>
      <description>Homemade Crunchwrap Supreme Inspired by this Reddit post.&#xA;Ingredients 1 Burrito-sized flour tortilla 1 Taco-sized flour tortilla 1 Taco-sized corn tortilla Ground beef Taco seasoning Pepper jack nacho cheese Greek yogurt OR sour cream OR guacamole Shredded lettuce Diced tomato Instructions Shred the lettuce and dice the tomatoes. Season the ground beef and cook it. Construct the layers: First layer: Burrito sized tortilla. Second layer: Seasoned ground beef spread out from center....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Chicken Parm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/slow_cooker_chicken_parm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 23:41:34 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/slow_cooker_chicken_parm/</guid>
      <description>Slow Cooker Chicken Parm Ingredients 2x Chicken Breast Packs (4 breasts) 1 Cans Trader Joes Marinara Sauce 1 Can Trader Joe&amp;rsquo;s Vodka Sauce Pasta (Spaghetti) Salt and Pepper Instructions Mix both sauces into slow cooker Season chicken breasts with salt and pepper Place chicken breasts in slow cooker, submerging underneath sauce Cover and set to LOW for 4 hours Do NOT lock the lid in place with the clasps After 3....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Tortilla Soup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/chicken_tortilla_soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:28:25 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/chicken_tortilla_soup/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Tortilla Soup Ingredients Tortilla chips / strips 1 Tbsp olive oil 1 medium onion, chopped 3 garlic cloves, minced 1 jalapeno pepper , seeded and diced 1 tsp ground cumin 1 tsp chilli powder 1 lb chicken breasts, (2 medium) 20 oz can crushed tomatoes 32 oz chicken broth 14 oz can black beans, drained and rinsed 1/2 cup cilantro, chopped, divided (reserve 1/4 of it for garnish) 1 lime, juiced 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 large avocado, diced 1 lime, cut into wedges, to serve Instructions Finely chop onion, garlic, jalapeño....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baked Honey Granola</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/baked_honey_granola/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:22:28 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/baked_honey_granola/</guid>
      <description>Baked Honey Granola Ingredients 2 Cups uncooked rolled oats Quarter cup brown sugar (or regular sugar) Do an eigth of a cup for less sweet granola Quarter teaspoon cinnamon Quarter cup of honey Quarter cup of olive oil Pinch of salt (Optional) Any dried mixins (e.g. dried fruit) Instructions Preheat oven to 325 degrees In large bowl, combine oats, brown sugar, cinnamon, salt In a glass measuring cup, add honey, and warm in microwave for 30 seconds Add the olive oil to the honey and stir to mix Drizzle the honey+olive oil over the ingredients....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Programmatically Bookmark, Archive and Share Websites</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/programmatic_bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 22:31:19 -0800</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/programmatic_bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>For the last decade plus, I’ve been tossing links to interesting pages in all sorts of random places. Firefox bookmarks, Apple Notes, Apple Reminders, Markdown files, emails to myself…&#xA;I figured it was finally time to organize all of that. Plus I’ve also wanted to add more content to my personal website for awhile. With my bookmarked links now organized in a single place, it was easy to auto-generate my bookmarks page....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bookmarks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>N/A (Matthew Peyton)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>Business Business &amp;gt; Case Studies 12 Startups in 12 Months Josh Schertz 12 Startups in 12 Months yongfook A Year of Making Is Done Apple, Samsung, and the Irrelevance of the American Smartphone Market From bootstrapped to a $425 million exit - The Trello story Here&amp;rsquo;s How I Bootstrapped a SaaS to $10k MRR - Bannerbear Here&amp;rsquo;s Why Firefox is Seeing a Continuous Decline for Last 12 Years How Superhuman Grows - by Jaryd Hermann - How They Grow How an Ugly Single-Page Website Makes $5,000 a Month with Affiliate Marketing I&amp;rsquo;m Launching 12 Startups in 12 Months Laleh Khalili · In Clover: What does McKinsey do?...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>